Hi everyone. We have Trayvon Walker
available. Please raise your hand if you
have a question.
We can start off with Jamal.
What's up Trayvon? Congratulations, man.
How's it feel to to kind of know that
you're going to be in Jacksonville for
for some time to come?
My family was probably like 2-3 years
ago. I was like if I can, I definitely
love to be in Jacksonville for the rest
of my career. Look at God.
And
Liam Cohen last week, he talked a little
bit about your end of season meeting
with him. Said you guys spent like 2
hours talking, talked about guys like
Aaron Donald. What did you take from
that conversation?
Man, it's just like taking my game to
another level. Obviously, he's he's seen
Aaron Donald. He coached helped He was
on the team with with Aaron Donald or
whatever. So, it just kind of helped put
things in perspective for me to be able
to just click it to a different type of
mindset was from how I was
going throughout the year or whatever
and I feel like that it really clicked
dawned on me that it's just time to take
wrap things up take take it to the next
level.
I do appreciate it Trayvon.
Congratulations, man. Thank you.
We'll go to D-Rock then to Shipley.
Hey Trayvon, congrats.
Was this a
quicker process than you might have
thought it would have been? Did you
think this might be one of those
you know, negotiations that kind of drag
on for a while? Me personally, like I
really didn't get too deep into the
negotiation part. I just let my agent
handle that and
they did what they did what they did and
I mean it was going to happen on God's
timing anyways. I'm firm believer in God
and everything. It just
took it took its own it did its own
race.
Does it take a weight off your mind at
all that it's done now and that you
don't have to we're not asking you about
it in June, July, August and stuff? I
mean I definitely say it takes some
weight off of my mind. Not not saying
that I was really too concerned about it
cuz I mean eventually I know it was
going to happen regardless of however
much or whatever, but just like having
it out of the way the money part all of
the talks about the money like it's just
time to go play ball now. I don't have
to think about none of that.
Like I said, it's just time to go play
ball now.
And one more real quick back to what
Jamal was saying about Liam talking
about Aaron Donald. He said he wants to
have to take you out of practice because
you're destroying their practice and
ability to practice. I mean how
What does that mean to you? I mean that
that's got to be pretty high praise when
he mentions you and Aaron Donald and
says yeah, Aaron Donald made it so we
couldn't practice and now I want Trayvon
to do the same thing. It's just
predominance, man. It's it's just also
it's it's helping everybody else on the
team get better while it's helping me
get better as well. Like I said, it's
just predominance and everybody that
plays in this league wants to be great,
wants to be hopefully that's everybody's
mindset to be great in the end and I
think that's that's really what he was
getting to when he was speaking on that.
Thanks bud. Appreciate it. Sir, thank
you.
Shipley then to O'Halloran.
Shipley, I think you're still muted. Oh,
sorry.
Trayvon, congratulations and thanks for
doing this. You said that you know,
you've known for a few years that
Jacksonville is where you wanted to be.
What does it say to you that you know,
even with new people coming in last
year, they pretty quickly showed that
same belief in you that they wanted you
here?
Can you say that one more time for me?
Sorry.
Yeah,
you said a few that you knew for a few
years that this is where you wanted to
be. What does it say that even with a
new coach, new GM coming in you know,
just a year ago that did you pretty
quickly they it was a mutual feeling
that they wanted you here too? It really
means a lot cuz like you say getting a
new staff in like you it's always that
uncertainty and coming into the when
they first got here, I I feel like they
did a great job of just communicating
with me think of things and that kind of
already put in perspective to how that
relationship was going to go. Sometimes
you never really know how it's going to
go, but ever since they've been there, I
feel like we on my end and their end
we've been transparent with each other
and we just have cordial conversations
to where we can all just be comfortable
and that was one of Liam's main things
that like say what's on it speak your
mind and we'll go from there. And I feel
like
>> Appreciate it Trayvon. Yes, sir.
Hey Trayvon, a couple for you.
Late in the season, they moved you
inside on some passing downs next to
Josh. If you guys start doing that for
the full season, what kind of impact do
you think you could have as an interior
rusher? I think I can have an impact
wherever they put me. I don't care if
they put me in in the secondary. It's
all about versatility in this league or
whatever, but it's all about just being
versatile do whatever the team do
whatever I need to do to help the team.
So, a blitzing safety is on the table?
Say that again. A blitzing safety is on
the table?
>> Hey, if that's what we need then I'll do
whatever.
Last [clears throat] one for me is
you had a lot of pressures last year.
Your pressure rate was was pretty
decent.
What are you working on this off season
to to take that next step to to get back
to that double double digit sack totals?
Number one my main thing was just
working on getting healthy and then it's
just fine tuning those little small
details within my hands, eye
coordination, things of that nature.
Just trying to keep my twitch as far as
my strength,
wrist mobility, working on some a lot of
things, but it's basically just kind of
ironing out some small details. You
know, the further you get in your career
like it kind of get it gets harder to I
wouldn't say it gets harder to
continuously elevate. It's just like you
got to find those little small little
details within your game and
continuously work those things.
Thank you now.
Last one, Travis Holmes.
Congratulations on the extension
Trayvon. I just wanted to know like how
has your leadership style evolved since
you first initially entered the league
as a number one pick and now you have
the opportunity with the extension and
everything else and just being that
leader on the field to also mentor the
younger players.
Man, I think for me it's just kind of a
I wouldn't even say a more vocal me.
It's just like obviously leading by
example. I know what
what's expected in the league. I know
what's expected from a leadership
standpoint. I know what's expected from
this this staff that we have and I just
try to go out there and be the best
version of me every day and I feel like
I've been a leader at my whole life. So,
a lot of things just really translate to
talking to the players players coming to
me asking questions. It's just about me
opening up telling them things that I
went through.
Just maybe say if I was a rookie or
whatever, but that's really all it is.
No, appreciate it. And also with the
two the back-to-back two sack seasons
and then having the multiple injuries
dealt dealt with in this past you know,
2025 season like how did that impact you
or did that impact you at all in you
know, as far as the mental as far as
your off season preparation and all of
that?
I mean
it definitely affected me with the
injuries, but just coming out going
having two back-to-back double digit
sack seasons then coming off a season
like last year. It's just always
I mean it's football. It's a 100% injury
rate. You know those injuries going to
be there, but you just got to
continuously fight through those things
and that's what I tried my best to do
and like long as I'm not putting the
team in a bad position in my eyes to
jeopardize winning games or whatever.
I'm going to always try my best to be
out there on the field regardless of
banged up hurt or not cuz everybody
around the league at a certain point in
the season is going to be banged up at
some point. So, I just try to keep
going.
I appreciate you. Congratulations. Sir,
thank you.
That's everyone. Thanks, Tray. Thank you
all.